<sburb description="Voice Dialogue">

	<action class='AKVEgg1' command= 'talk' name='Ask Karkat Voice'>
	<args>
	@karkat_talk KARKAT: WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO BE.
	@voice_talk VOICE: YOUR VOICE.
	@karkat_horror KARKAT: WHAT? WHOA. HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
	@voice_idle VOICE: I’VE HAD ABOUT 9 MONTHS OF PRACTICE.
	@karkat_what KARKAT: PRACTICE BEING ME?
	@voice_idle VOICE: PRETTY MUCH, YEAH.
	@karkat_talk KARKAT: CAN YOU... STOP?
	@voice_talk VOICE: Yeah, anytime.
	@karkat_talk KARKAT: THAT’S A LOT LESS CREEPY, THANK YOU.
	@voice_idle VOICE: No probs.
	@karkat_what KARKAT: SO... HOW ARE YOU HERE?
	@voice_talk VOICE: Canonically, I’m not. I’m in a blank space that isn’t part of the game. The walk map just permits you could go up here so I thought I’d just chill here.
	@karkat_what KARKAT: ...
	@voice_idle VOICE: What?
	@karkat_talk KARKAT: SO YOU’RE PART OF THE FANDOM THING I HEARD ABOUT IN THE OTHER ROOM?
	@voice_talk VOICE: Fanon, yeah.
	@karkat_talk KARKAT: YOU MUST BE PRETTY BIG IN FANON TO BE ABLE TO SHOW UP HERE...
	@voice_talk VOICE: Not very. A lot of people seem to think I pull you off well, though. They call that having a “headcanon voice.” When people read your text, they hear my voice in their head. It’s one of the best compliments to get as a voice actor. Up there with “This made me cry” and “This made me want to read Homestuck.”
	@voice_idle VOICE: Some people prefer other voice actors for you. A lot of people try it out. I was a bit late in the game, actually. A lot of other more experienced actors have been around longer and have their foot planted pretty solid in Karkat territory. I’m lucky I have what I have.
	@karkat_yell KARKAT: TERRITORY? PEOPLE HAVE TO LIKE PROVE THEMSELVES TO EACH OTHER TO LIKE... CLAIM ME?
	@voice_idle VOICE: To claim part of your fandom, really.
	@karkat_yell KARKAT: AND WHAT VALLIANT BULLSHIT DID YOU PULL OFF TO DO THAT?
	@voice_talk VOICE: I pioneered a genre of “Ask-Blogs” specifically for voice actors to gain recognition independently, that forces them to think more about the character and study them more than you would have to from doing Comic Dubs or Pesterlog readings. It’s like writing your own fanfiction to 15 different prompts once an update and then voice acting it.
	@voice_idle VOICE: I focus on writing you as faithful to canon as I can, and acting off of that. I think that’s really the key to portraying you. That’s why I got into this whole Karkat business. Just didn’t think anyone was doing it true enough to you. Wanted to do you justice.
	@karkat_what KARKAT: SO YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE BETTER THAN EVERYONE ELSE?
	@voice_idle VOICE: I’m not sure that’s a fair way to phrase it. I did look up to quite a few people and pull from a few I thought were on the right track. Such as Broadway Karkat.
	@karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: RIGHT, THE PINK SPARKLY ONE.
	@voice_talk VOICE: Ah, you remember! But yes, Broadway Karkat is another popular variation of you in this fandom. There are a few other varieties.
	@voice_idle VOICE: Karkat is also commonly available in a variety of flavors produced by a number of brands with varying degrees of quality. You can pick up one or two going through any tag on tumblr.
	@karkat_yell KARKAT: SHIT, THERE’S A LOT OF ME OUT THERE...
	@karkat_talk KARKAT: WHAT EXACTLY IS YOUR VARIETY, THOUGH?
	@voice_talk VOICE: Well... it’s this! It’s what’s on this blog!
	@karkat_yell KARKAT: BUT, I MEAN... WHO THE FUCK ARE YOU? 
	@voice_idle VOICE: Oh, we’re going this route, aren’t we?
	@karkat_what KARKAT: ...
	
	
	@case_talk CASE: I go by “Case” normally.
	@karkat_horror KARKAT: WHOA.
	@case_huh CASE: What?
	@karkat_talk KARKAT: YOU LOOK LIKE SOME FREAK COMBINATION OF STRIDER AND EGBERT.
	@case_slytalk CASE: Oh. Yeah. I get that a lot.
	@karkat_what KARKAT: SO, JUST SO I CAN CHECK WHERE I’M AT HERE...
	@karkat_talk KARKAT: YOU’RE A REAL PERSON, WHO’S A FAN OF A COMIC THAT I’M IN...
	@karkat_yell KARKAT: WHO RUNS A BLOG WHERE YOU WRITE AND VOICE ACT AS ME?
	@case_idle CASE: Yes. 
	@karkat_talk KARKAT: SO IT’S NOT MY BLOG, IT’S YOURS.
	@case_slytalk CASE: It’s yours just as much as it is mine.
	@karkat_what KARKAT: ... 
	@karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: ARE YOU GOING TO GET ALL SENTIMENTAL OVER ME NOW?
	@case_slytalk CASE: Karkat, you are a character who’s not just enjoyed by people in a webcomic, but an anchor for the fandom you’re in and one of the most relatable characters to the comic’s fans. 
	@case_talk CASE: The emotional struggles the world has seen you go through has made a lot of people feel like they know you personally. You represent the issues a lot of members of the young adult audience face.
	@case_huhtalk CASE: So the fact is, people don’t come to that blog to talk to me. In fact, up until this point, I have never once on that blog mentioned myself as its creator or linked back to my main blog. Because it’s not me they’re talking to. It’s not my views. It’s not my voice. It’s not my emotions.
	@case_talk CASE: It’s you. The world cares about you. Tumblr wants you.
	@case_talk CASE: You’re the one talking.
	@case_sly CASE: I’m just the one hitting the publish button.
	@karkat_sullen KARKAT:
	@case_slytalk CASE: (And right now I’m kind of a shameless self-insert, too)
	@karkat_what KARKAT:
	@case_slytalk CASE: You don’t have to say anything. Just keep up what you do.
	</args>
	<!-- warp karkat back somewhere else -->
	</action>

	<action class='AKVEGG2' command='talk' name='Ask Case for credits'>
	<args>
@karkat_talk KARKAT: DON’T YOU WANT TO TAKE ANY CREDIT AFTER A YEAR OF DOING THIS?
@case_slytalk CASE: How about instead I just name drop everyone else.
@case_slytalk CASE: I already mentioned Zanney, but I will again. Zanney was the first person I met through the Homestuck fandom and I am very glad I did. In addition to being a talented vocalist, you’ll never meet a more passionate and dedicated vocalist and person in general.
@case_idle CASE: Zanney @ broadwaykarkat.tumblr.com
@case_slytalk CASE: Someone I got introduced to right after the blog exploded, who I think helped the blog explode, was Kylee Henke, who’s a a triple threat of art, music, and acting. She’s also pretty rad as-is.
@case_idle CASE: Kylee Henke @ kyleehenke.tumblr.com
@case_slytalk CASE: LOVAC was the first voice acting troupe I ever got into, which has quite a few awesome people involved. One was on my album!
@case_idle CASE: lovac @ LandOfVoiceAndCans.tumblr.com
@case_slytalk CASE: Another exceptional Homestuck writer, who I met through feeling sad for Karkat and sending them awestruck messages about their writing...
@case_slytalk CASE: Is of course Fivetail, of BoyfriendLeaders, Sadstuck, and general JohnKat fame. She’s done a LOT to support me since we met, and we’ve traded quite a few writing ideas from each other. It’s also no secret she writes Karkat just based off of Me and not actually Karkat. Because seriously. Gordon Ramsay? Cello? Glasses? Come on.
@case_talk CASE: Love you, Fivetail.
@case_idle CASE: Fivetail @ fivetail.tumblr.com, boyfriendleaders.tumblr.com, johnkarkat.com, sadstuck.tumblr.com
@case_slytalk CASE: Kinomatika is really cool because she’s really cool because she’s really cool because she’s really cool because she draws really cool because she’s really cool and she also sent me an acoustic guitar for free once. And she’s also one of the coolest people I’ve met on the internet in general. Totally not one of them vegans.
@case_idle CASE: Kino @ Kinomatika.tumblr.com
@case_slytalk CASE: Dante Basco is my favorite follower for reasons you already know because you’re a Homestuck. He’s Rufio, Zuko, Jake Llong, and also a kickass poet as well as a kickass actor.
@case_idle CASE: Dante Basco @ rufiozuko.tumblr.com
@case_huhtalk CASE: Now the voice actors. Oh jeez.
@case_slytalk CASE: Afina and Tooch are my fellow ask-bloggers and we all bros, both are sick to work with.
@case_idle CASE: Afina @ 4SKT3R3Z1VO1C3.tumblr.com, celestialtoxophilite.tumblr.com. Tooch @ askstridervoice.tumblr.com, miketooch.tumblr.com
@case_talk CASE: Denten is a pro. He’s in a game for the xbox. That pro. He’s also the greatest John voice actor by objectionable fact because his name is John and also because he’s a fantastic voice actor.
@case_idle CASE: Denten @ Denten02.tumblr.com
@case_madtalk CASE: JAMES. ERIDAN. BRITISH. ALSO KICKASS MUSICIAN WITH GODLY MIXING SKILLS. ALSO FUCKING DEAD DESPITE POPULAR BELIEF.
@case_idle CASE: James @ everyoneLovesRobots.tumblr.com
@case_talk CASE: Maddi. Lyricist. Vocalist. Actor. Kanaya extraordinaire. 
@case_idle CASE: maddi @ kitsubasa.tumblr.com
@case_talk CASE: Finally, major co-developer of this game, Andrew. I met him through this project and shortly found out what an amazing person he was. Let the fact that this game even got done be a testament to that.
@case_idle CASE: Andrew @ mageOfForm.tumblr.com
@case_talk CASE: And a few more odd special thanks just to tack you guys on. Fugiman is p cool, Headrebel, you’re p cool.
@case_slytalk CASE: Omar I know you aren’t playing, but anyone else who is should post a screenshot of this part on the AKV tag even if there are more already there so I can reblog them an fill his dash with it. Hi Omar.
@case_talk CASE: Thanks Michael for planting that one seed in my head that I should both get into Homestuck and get into voice acting.
@case_slytalk CASE: And thank you THE FUCKING MOST to Andrew Hussie for not only Homestuck and all the amazing opportunities its fandom has brought me, but more specifically for making Karkat’s actions in the story since I started this blog so incredibly convenient for me to fit this blog into a way that makes sense in canon. It’s almost like you’re doing it just for me. It works all too perfectly. We love you, Hussie.
@karkat_what KARKAT: AND WHAT ABOUT YOU?
@case_huh CASE: Hm?
@karkat_talk KARKAT: AREN’T YOU GOING TO DO A LINK BACK TO YOURSELF OR...
@case_slytalk CASE: They can find me. I’ll be around.
@karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: ...
@case_talk CASE: But yeah, thanks everyone, for making this past year the greatest thing that’s happened to me. For everyone who bought my album, you’re getting me through college in tough times. For anyone who’s so much as reblogged any of my posts, you’ve helped me grow. For anyone who’s supported me both through the greatest of praise and the harshest of critique, I thank you for helping me improve.
@case_madtalk CASE: Now you, get back the fuck into canon.
	<args>
	</action>
</sburb>