<sburb description='Interaction Dialogue'>
	<classes>
	
	<!-- Easter Egg Dialogue -->
	
		        <action class='computer1' command="talk">
           <args>
               @! This looks familiar...
               @! wrigglerbase, hemoglobin, hemogoblin (avoiid at all co2t2), redgrub, nubhub (ha2 omorashi 2tuff)...
               @! This is from that one time sollux asked you if you knew any porn sites that were easy to get to.
               @! What the fuck does omorashi mean?
               @! Probably best you leave that unanswered.
           </args>
        </action>
       
       <action class='computer2' command="talk">
           <args>
               @! There appear to be some lyrics written on this one.
               @! WHEN I WAS A YOUNG GRUB...
               @! I'D ALWAYS IMAGINED THAT I'D GROW UP-
               @! You've heard these before.
           </args>
       </action>
       
       <action class='computer3' command="talk">
           <args>
               @! More lyrics on this one, it looks like.
               @! Some indie shit about insomnia or something.
               @! Pass.
           </args>
       </action>
	          
		<action class='computer3a' command="talk">
           <args>
               @! There's reasons why we fell so far so fast. There's reasons why the plusses never last. I take my own thoughts with a grain of salt, when I tell myself that this is all my fault.
			   @! There's reasons for these bags under my eyes. It's the effort I don't give except in lies. Maybe it's the weight of all the promises we couldn't keep.
			   @! But the universe will not let me sleep.
           </args>
       </action>
       
       
       <action class='computer4' command='talk'>
           <args>
               @! There is an IM conversation open...
            @!~gameplan
               @! ANDREW: if you don't want there to be a loading time inbetween lowaa happening, just put it on the same image as the roof.
               @! CASE: I wouldn't mind a loading time really
               @! ANDREW: also what are the little red arrows?
               @! CASE: the red arrows are the opposing team attacking the linebacker
               @! CASE: obvs
               @! ANDREW: oh. how ever did i miss that.
               @! ANDREW: this is some a+ strategy you got going on there.  we're sure to win in the playoffs with your brilliance on our side.
               @! Dumb.
               
            </args>
        </action>
		
		<!-- Lab 1 Object Dialogue -->
			
			<action class='crabphone' command='talk'>
				<args>
	</classes>
</sburb>
