<sburb description='Easter Egg logs'>
	<classes>
	
		        <action class='sollux1' command="Ask where you are">
           <args>
				@sollux_pun SOLLUX: 2up kk, welcome two the fandom room.
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: WHAT THE HELL DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
				@sollux_lisp SOLLUX: iit mean2 that ba2iically, nothiing iin here could be con2iidered canon. iit’2 kiind of like a...
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: WHAT ABOUT CANNONS?
				@karkat_yell KARKAT: WHAT IN THE FUCK ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: ACTUALLY, WAIT A SECOND. DIDN’T YOU LOSE YOUR EYES AND TEETH?
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: HAVE YOU BEEN IN THIS LAB THE WHOLE TIME?
				
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: kk ii ju2t fuckiing told you.
				@karkat_yell KARKAT: I DON’T EVEN REMEMBER THIS ROOM EXISTING.
				@sollux_madtalk SOLLUX: hey maybe you 2hould 2hut your flutteriing 2eedflap and let me 2peak.
				@karkat_shout KARKAT: NO, I HAVE TOO MANY QUESTIONS.
				@sollux_shock SOLLUX: THEN LET ME FUCKIING AN2WER THEM, 2HIIT2PONGE
				@karkat_yell KARKAT: FUCK, OK, FINE!
				@karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: FINE... GO ON.
				@sollux_madtalk SOLLUX: alriight, what ii was tryiing two 2ay......
				@! They proceeded to have the most 4th wall breaking discussion in the history of walkaround games.
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: OH WOW. THAT’S ALL KIND OF FASCINATING ACTUALLY. IT CLEARS UP A LOT.
				@sollux_pun SOLLUX: there, 2ee? iit’2 not that hard two get. the down2iide ii2 that you won’t remember anythiing about what ii told you once you leave thii2 room.
				@karkat_what KARKAT: ... WHAT?
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: thii2 room doe2n’t exii2t iin canon, kk.
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: ... SO ALL THE TIME I JUST SPENT HERE WAS POINTLESS?
				@sollux_lisp SOLLUX: no tiime ha2 pa22ed iin canon 2iince you got here.
				@karkat_what KARKAT: ...
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: iif you 2omehow wander back here you’ll 2tiill remember what went on here though.
				@sollux_lisp SOLLUX: but what happen2 iin the fandom, 2tay2 iin the fandom.
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: unle22 that orange guy deciide2 two iintegrate iit iintwo canon.
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: whiich ii am certaiin wiil never be the ca2e wiith thii2 room.
				@karkat_what KARKAT: ...
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: I GUESS I’ll KEEP THAT IN MIND?
				@karkat_idle KARKAT: ONE MORE QUESTION.
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: WHY THE FUCK ARE YOU THE ONE EXPLAINING THIS TO ME?
				@sollux_pun SOLLUX: becau2e iim the voiice’2 favoriite character.
				@karkat_what KARKAT: WAIT, THE VOICES OR THE VOICE’S?
				@sollux_pun SOLLUX: oh look at that you're piickiing up on thiing2.
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: for all you know thii2 room miight be ba2ed off 2omethiing from a 2olkat rp.
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: thiink about that for a whiile, kk.
				@karkat_what KARKAT: DO NOT TELL ME THAT "SOLKAT" MEANS WHAT I THINK IT MEANS...
				@sollux_pun SOLLUX: oh iit can mean whatever you want iit two, kk.
				@karkat_horror KARKAT: ...
				@karkat_facepalm KARKAT: FUCK, I...
				@! You need a second to let your mind clear.
           	</args>
          	<action command='removeAction'>
           		<args>sollux,Ask where you are.</args>
           		<action command='addAction'>
           			<args>sollux,
           				<action class='sollux2' command='talk' name='Get Hints'>
           				</action>
           			</args>
           			<action command='addAction'>
           				<args>sollux,
           					<action class='sollux3' command='talk' name='Ask about style.'>
           					</action>
           				</args>
           				<action command='addAction'>
           					<args>sollux,
           						<action class='sollux4' command='talk' name='Ask personal question.'>
           						</action>
           					</args>
           				</action>
           			</action>
           		</action>
           	</action>
        </action>
		
		<!-- after this conversation others open up -->
		 <action class='sollux2' command="Get Hints">
		   <args>
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: OK, SO IS THIS THE ONLY PLACE THAT IS JUST MAGICALLY NOT CANON?
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: ii know ii 2aiid you won’t remember anythiing that happen2 out2iide thii2 room 2o iit would not even matter iif ii told you.
				@sollux_lisp SOLLUX: but no, there’2 another 2ecret nearby.
				@sollux_pun SOLLUX: and two fiind iit you have two tell the diifference between goiing _up_ and goiing _up_.
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: there you may fiind a voiice.
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: THIS IS WAY TOO CRYPTIC FOR ME TO UNDERSTAND.
				@sollux_madtalk SOLLUX: well iif ii gave iit away, iit wouldn’t be a 2ecret, would iit?
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: iit’2 a 2ecret two everyone.
				@karkat_what KARKAT: I CAN’T ASK FOR ANY MORE HINTS?
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: maybe, maybe not...
				@sollux_pun SOLLUX: let'2 ju2t 2ay ii warned you, bro.
			</args>
		</action>
		
			 <action class='sollux3' command="Ask about style">
		   <args>
					@sollux_talk SOLLUX: 밤에는 따사로운 인간적인 여자. 커피 한잔의 여유를 아는 품격 있는 여자. 낮이 오면 심장이 뜨거워지는 여자. 그런 반전 있는 여자.
					@karkat_what KARKAT: WHAT? I’M NOT SURE I UNDERSTOOD THAT.
					@sollux_talk SOLLUX: 나는 트롤이. 낮에는 너만큼 따사로운 그런 트롤이. 커피 식기도 전에 원샷 때리는 트롤이. 밤이 오면 심장이 터져버리는 트롤이. 그런 트롤이.
					@karkat_talk KARKAT: DUDE I’M NOT GETTING ANY OF THIS, SLOW DOWN!
					@sollux_talk SOLLUX: 아름다워 사랑스러워. 
					@karkat_talk KARKAT: SOLLUX ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING TO ME?
					@sollux_talk SOLLUX: 그래 너.
					@karkat_yell KARKAT: HEY.
					@sollux_talk SOLLUX: 그래 바로 너.
					@karkat_shout KARKAT: HEY!
					@sollux_talk SOLLUX: 아름다워 사랑스러워.
					@karkat_shout KARKAT: YOU’RE DOING THIS JUST TO FUCK WITH ME AREN’T YOU?
					@sollux_talk SOLLUX: 그래 너.
					@karkat_yell KARKAT: NO.
					@sollux_pun SOLLUX:그래 바로 너.
					@karkat_shout KARKAT: FUCKING STOP!
					@sollux_pun SOLLUX: 지금부터 갈 데까지 가볼까...
					@sollux_pun SOLLUX: ...
					@karkat_idle KARKAT: ...
					@karkat_what KARKAT: ARE YOU DONE?
					@sollux_pun SOLLUX: 오빠 캎터남스타일!
					@karkat_shout KARKAT: SOLLUX, SHUT THE FUCK UP!
					@sollux_talk SOLLUX: thii2 i2 the 2ong of my people kk.
					@karkat_yell KARKAT: WHAT?
					@sollux_pun SOLLUX: iit i2 liike the holy anthem of 2wag.
					@karkat_yell KARKAT: WHAT IN HOLY BULGEMUNCHING FUCK IS SWAG?
					@sollux_talk SOLLUX: eh, nevermiind.
			</args>
		</action>
		
		<action class='sollux4' command="Ask personal question">
		   	<args>
		   		@karkat_idle KARKAT: SO... 
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: ... yeah?
				@karkat_talk KARKAT: CAN I ASK YOU A SERIOUS QUESTION?
				@sollux_talk SOLLUX: ii don't have two bulge2, kk.
				@karkat_idle KARKAT: OH. OK.
		   
		   	</args>
		</action>

	</classes>
</sburb>
