<sburb description='tavros logs'>
	<classes>
		  <action class='tavrosTalk1' sprite='tavros' command='talk'>
			 <!-- triggered automatically when entering far right room-->
			 <args>
			  		@tavros_blink TAVROS: hEY,,,

					@karkat_horror KARKAT: FUCK!
					
					@karkat_yell KARKAT: TAVROS WHERE THE FUCK DID YOU COME FROM?
					
					@tavros_talk TAVROS: i,,, tHINK MY BUBBLE MUST HAVE SWEPT THROUGH THIS ONE,,,
					
					@tavros_blink TAVROS: aND, nOW I’M HERE I GUESS,
					
					@karkat_facepalm KARKAT: THIS IS THE DUMBEST FUCKING CLUSTERFUCK REUNION EVER.
					
					@karkat_what KARKAT: WAIT TAVROS, WHERE THE FUCK ARE YOUR PANTS?
					
					@eridan_huh ERIDAN: yeah wwhat the hell kind of getup is that dirtblood
					@eridan_talk ERIDAN: that looks so ridiculous
					
					@tavros_talk TAVROS: oH, iT’S MY GOD TIER OUTFIT,
					@tavros_talk2 TAVROS: wHEN I GOT TO IT I GOT LEGS AGAIN, aND I GUESS THE GAME WANTED ME TO NOTICE OR SOMETHING,
					@tavros_sadtalk TAVROS: pANTS WOULD BE, nICE THOUGH,
					
					@karkat_facepalm KARKAT: I’M SORRY BUT I CAN’T EVEN LOOK AT YOU, YOU’RE JUST EMBARRASSING.
					
					@tavros_sadtalk TAVROS: yEAH, i KNOW,
					
					@karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: THIS JUST KEEPS GETTING MORE AND MORE AWKWARD.
					
					@karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: I’LL JUST CATCH THE NEXT DEAD ERIDAN THAT DRIFTS BY, I’M GOING BACK DOWNSTAIRS.
					
					@eridan_fingers ERIDAN: no kar
					@eridan_fingers ERIDAN: you don’t havve to be like that
					
					@karkat_talk KARKAT: YES I DO.
					@karkat_yell KARKAT: WATCH ME, MAGICALLY BECOME ABSENT FROM THIS SHITTY DREAM PLANET WITH PANTLESS DEAD FRIENDS. LATER, FUCKERS!
					@! You storm out, leaving your parallel dead friends in their bubble.

				
		 	</args>
			<!-- control given back to player, observation deck stairs open again -->
		 </action>
		 
		 
		 <action class='tavrosTalk2' sprite='tavros' command='talk'>
			 <!-- [focus switches as you leave LOWAA]-->
			 <args>
		 
				@eridan_idle ERIDAN: wwell...
				
				@tavros_sad TAVROS: uH,,,
				
				@eridan_huh ERIDAN: oh he dropped that wweird thing he wwas holdin
				
				@tavros_talk TAVROS: wELL, uM, mAYBE WE SHOULD,, STOP IT FOR HIM,,,
				
				@eridan_talk ERIDAN: wwait wwhy not try and go through it so wwe can see wwhat he’s been up to
				
				@tavros_sadtalk TAVROS: tHAT WOULDN’T BE A VERY COOL THING,, TO DO TO HIM,
				
				@eridan_talk ERIDAN: i just wwant to see wwhat hes been recordin
				@eridan_talk ERIDAN: if its a public thing he probably wwouldn’t care if wwe saw
				@eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwere dead anywway
				
				@tavros_sadtalk TAVROS: tHAT IS A GOOD POINT,
		 
		 	</args>
			<!-- switch rooms -->
		 </action>
		 
		 
		</classes>
</sburb>