<sburb description="lowaa">

    <dependencies>
        <dependency>chars/karkat.xml</dependency>

        <!-- get rid of those -->
        <dependency>chars/dave.xml</dependency>
        <dependency>chars/terezi.xml</dependency>
        <dependency>chars/eridan.xml</dependency>
        <dependency>chars/tavros.xml</dependency>

    </dependencies>
    
    <assets>

        <asset name='lowaa_BG_0_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/lowaa_BG.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_0_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_0_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_0_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_0_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_0_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_0_3.png</asset>

        <asset name='lowaa_BG_1_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_1_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_1_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_1_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_1_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_1_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_1_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_1_3.png</asset>

        <asset name='lowaa_BG_2_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_2_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_2_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_2_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_2_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_2_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_2_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_2_3.png</asset>
        
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_3_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_3_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_3_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_3_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_3_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_3_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_3_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_3_3.png</asset>
        
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_4_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_4_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_4_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_4_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_4_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_4_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_4_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_4_3.png</asset>

        
        
        <asset name='lowaa_WM' type='graphic'>backgrounds/lowaa_WM3.png</asset>
        
        
        
        
    </assets>
    
    
    
    
    
    
    <rooms>

        <room name='lowaa' walkableMap='lowaa_WM' scale='4'>


            <triggers>
                <trigger detonate='true'>spriteProperty,char,x&gt;1
                    <action class='tereziTalk3' command='talk' noDelay='true'>
                    </action>
                </trigger>
                
                
            </triggers>
            

            <character class='karkat' x='500' y='920'>
                <action class='beKarkat'/>
            </character>

            <!-- eridan 980 x 790 -->
            <character class='eridan' x='50' y='50'>
                <action name='Talk to Eridan.' command='talk'>
                    <args>
                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: so kar are you all alivve
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: like actually alivve

                        @karkat_what KARKAT: YEAH...

                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: wwhat a fuckin relief for once
                        @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: all the other bubbles i cross through wwent through timelines so different
                        @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: and they all don’t remember jack shit about wwhat happened

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: IT’S THE SAME WITH THE FEW VERSIONS OF YOU THAT I’VE MET. I DOUBT WE WENT THROUGH ANY OF THE SAME FUCKING STUFF YOU DID.

                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: i don’t knoww
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: i guess it just feels more genuine or something
                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: you look older though

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: WE’VE BEEN OUT HERE FOR OVER HALF A SWEEP.
                        @karkat_what KARKAT: I THINK THAT’S ABOUT A YEAR AND A FEW MONTHS IN HUMAN TIME.

                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwhats a human

                        @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: UGH...

                        @karkat_yell KARKAT: THESE PALE MOTHERFUCKERS LIKE THE GUY IN THE RED GEAR PAJAMAS.

                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: are they game constructs or

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: NO, THEY’RE FROM A DIFFERENT UNIVERSE.

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: THE ONE WE FUCKING CREATED WHEN WE WON THE GAME.

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: BUT THROUGH A COMBINATION OF ME FUCKING UP AND THEM FUCKING UP...

                        @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: WE NEVER REALLY FULLY WON.

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: SO WE’VE BEEN WORKING WITH THEM ON CHEATING THE SYSTEM.

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: IT’S A LONG AND INCREDIBLY CONVOLUTED STORY THAT WOULD PROBABLY TAKE NEARLY 2 SWEEPS AND EIGHT THOUSAND PAGES TO TELL ACCURATELY.

                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: i think i get it

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: GOOD, BECAUSE I DON’T.

                        @! You start to wonder if Terezi’s noticed Eridan’s arrival. If anything is going to interrupt her RP streak, this will.
                    </args>
                    <action command='follow'>
                        <args>eridan,char</args>
                        <action command='removeAction'>
                            <args>eridan,Talk to Eridan.</args>
                        </action>
                    </action>
                </action>

            </character>

            <character class='terezi' x='869' y='771'/>

            <character class='dave' x='918' y='841'>
                <action class='daveTalk2' command='talk' name='Talk to Dave.'>

                    <args>
                        @dave_smug DAVE: so who the fuck’s memories are these? im kind of digging the set 

                        @dave_talk DAVE: im gettin this hunchback of notre dame vibe except for gargoyles that come to life and completely ruin the movie its a bunch of weird black winged monster things.

                        @dave_concern DAVE: hey have we been here before?

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: ACTUALLY WE HAVE. IT’S WHERE THE MAYOR WAS REVIVED.

                        @dave_talk DAVE: ah right cool

                        @dave_talk DAVE: for real though

                        @dave_smug DAVE: these palaces or whatever are some legitimately class shit here

                        @dave_smug DAVE: like some “i feel like i should be waiting for a science professor to show up” level of class

                        @karkat_horror KARKAT: DON’T SAY THAT WORD TOO LOUD!
                        @karkat_yell KARKAT: IT COULD BE A FUCKING DUCK CALL AROUND HERE, YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL.

                        @dave_huh DAVE: what class

                        @karkat_shout KARKAT: NO, YOU IDIOT-

                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: i’m certainly no professor but i do knoww quite a bit about science
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: is there currently a discussion going on
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: i wwouldn’t mind joining in

                        @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: TOO LATE...

                        @dave_smug DAVE: oh yeah this douchebag
                        @dave_talk DAVE: hey weren’t you dressed like psyduck before 
                        @dave_concern DAVE: shit you probably dont remember do you
                        @dave_huhtalk DAVE: damn that wasn’t even technically you
                        @dave_huhtalk DAVE: i just confused myself there
                        @dave_mad DAVE: doomed timelines are stupid

                        @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: (like he'd even know what a fucking psyduck is...)

                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwait
                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwho...
                        @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: wwhat the hell kind of creature is that

                        @dave_smug DAVE: oh right you assholes couldnt even all stay alive before you actually met any of us could you

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: YEAH, HE PROBABLY DIED BEFORE SGRUB ENDED.

                        @dave_concern DAVE: alright then I got this

                        @dave_smug DAVE: greetings dead alternate timeline alien whose name i dont care about
                        i am dave s obana and i will be your ambassador to my species

                        @dave_smug DAVE: the pajama draped musclebreasted hollering phallus baboon

                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: pajama wwhat
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: hollerin wwhat
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: kar is this guy for real

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: HE’S A HUMAN, HE’S...
                        @karkat_what KARKAT: IT’S...
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: IT’S NOT IMPORTANT, JUST IGNORE HIM.

                        @dave_madtalk DAVE: dont try to undermine the importance of this inter-realm ambassadorship
                        @dave_madtalk DAVE: before you know it shits gonna go haywire and the afterlife is gonna explode or implode or crack apart or something and how are we gonna know about it? 
                        @dave_talk DAVE: gotta keep our shit tight with these white eyed folk

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: I COULD SIT HERE AND KEEP TELLING YOU HOW MUCH MORE IDIOTIC YOU KEEP SOUNDING, BUT YOU’D COME RIGHT BACK WITH EVEN MORE STUPID IRONIC RAMBLING AND I WOULD STILL THINK THE SAME THING BUT EVEN WORSE, AND IT WOULD BE A NO WIN SITUATION. 

                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: SO I THINK WHAT I’M GOING TO DO IS WALK AWAY NOW, TO MAKE SURE I DON’T SPARK ANY MORE OF YOUR TIRED AND SARCASTIC VERBAL ESSAYS ON IRRELEVANCE.

                        @dave_smug DAVE: suit yourself nubs
                    </args>

                    <action command='removeAction' >
                        <args>dave,Talk to Dave.</args>
                        <action command='moveSprite'> 
                            <args>eridan,980,790</args>
                           <!-- <action command='addAction' class='tereziTalk4' sprite='terezi'>
                                
                                fuuuuuck me this isnt working

                            </action>-->
                        </action>
                    </action>

                    
                    

                </action>
            </character>






            <!-- tavros 1650 x 1050 -->

            <character class='tavros' x='1680' y='1020'/>




            <sprite name='lowaa_BG'>
                <animation sheet='lowaa_BG' sliced='true' numCols='5' numRows='4' colSize='500' rowSize='500'/>
            </sprite>




        </room>
    </rooms>
</sburb>